keep-collective.com 2014-12-17

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy
Stella & Dot wants your experience with us to be nothing short of fabulous. We respect the
privacy of our Stella & Dot Family Brands Independent Business Owners, customers and those
who use our services. To this end, we have systems in place for securely managing your
Personal Information. We created this Privacy Policy to help you understand the types of
information we collect, how we use and disclose it, your options related to it, and our
responsibilities in safeguarding it.
This Privacy Policy is incorporated into our Terms of Use. All capitalized terms not defined in
this Privacy Policy have the meaning set forth in the Terms of Use.
This Privacy Policy applies to the Service, and it also applies to collection of your Personal
Information from offline sources as described in this Privacy Policy.
“Personal Information” means information that alone or when in combination with other
information may be used to readily identify, contact, or locate you, such as: name, address, email
address, or phone number. We do not consider Personal Information to include information that
has been anonymized so that it does not allow a third party to easily identify a specific individual.
COLLECTION OF INFORMATION
      We collect Personal Information when you:
             register to use the Service, place an order, or provide contact information to an
              Independent Business Owner;
             register as an Independent Business Owner or express interest in becoming an
              Independent Business Owner;
             use the Service; and
             communicate with us.
      We also collect information, such as anonymous usage statistics, by using cookies,
      server logs, and other similar technology as you use the Service.
You do not need to provide Personal Information to visit the Service. All Personal Information
gathered is on a voluntary basis. If you decide to provide us with your Personal Information, we
may store it through whatever means you provided such information (through our Service,
Independent Business Owner, via email or facsimile, etc.). By using the Service, submitting a
signed Customer Order Form to an Independent Business Owner, or submitting a new
Independent Business Owner Agreement to us, you also authorize us to gather, parse, retain, use,
and disclose information to provide the Service and our services as described in this Privacy
Policy, unless we are notified otherwise.
                                                   1

Customer Online Registration. To register as a customer on our Website, you may need to
provide Personal Information, such as your name, email address, and password. You may also
provide other optional information, such as your month and day of birth.
Customer Information from Independent Business Owners. Customers may complete and
sign a Customer Order Form at a Trunk Show and provide it to an Independent Business Owner.
The Independent Business Owner will submit the information to us through the Service so that
we may process your order. Customers may also provide their contact information to
Independent Business Owners without making a purchase, and Independent Business Owners
may save such information in their contact lists on the Service. All Independent Business
Owners must abide by this Privacy Policy and must not share information except in connection
with their Stella & Dot business.
Independent Business Owner Registration. To register as an Independent Business Owner on
our Service, you may need to provide Personal Information, such as your name, social security
number, tax identification number, date of birth, email address, telephone number, postal
address, and password. You may also provide other information, such as your photograph and
information in your completed and digitally signed on-line Independent Business Owner
Agreement. Upon the termination of the relationship between Stella & Dot and the Independent
Business Owner, Stella & Dot will keep the Independent Business Owner’s Personal Information
for lawful purposes only.
Expressing Interest in Becoming an Independent Business Owner. We collect any Personal
Information included in requests to learn more about being an Independent Business Owner or
hostess. Such information may be submitted to us through the Service or via email. You may
also provide Personal Information directly to a Stella & Dot Family Brands Independent
Business Owner.
Using the Service. We collect information you post through the Service. For example, when
customers sign up for a newsletter, post a photograph, or connect with an Independent Business
Owner, the Service will collect the information customers or Independent Business Owners
provide in such submissions, including any Personal Information.
Making Payments. When you make payments through the Service or complete a Customer
Order Form, your financial account information, such as your credit card number, will be
collected by our third-party payment processors. We do not collect or store such financial
account information, but we may receive information from our payment processor about the
payment, such as the date and time of payment.
Social Plug-Ins. The Website may allow you to use social media plug-ins, such as Facebook’s
“like” or Twitter’s “tweet” functions. The social media plug-ins collect information about you,
such as your IP address, when you use them. The privacy policies of the social media services,
and not this Privacy Policy, apply to any data collected by the social media plug-ins.
Social Media Pages. We may collect information about you when you visit our social media
pages or other features. The social media website provider may provide us with information,
                                                 2

including Personal Information, such as your name, email address, and other information made
available to us.
Customer Support. We may collect Personal Information through your communications with
our customer-support team.
Cookies and Similar Technology
We and our third party service providers, such as advertising networks and analytics service
providers, may collect anonymous information automatically through the use of “cookies” and
similar technology. The service providers also may collect information about your online
activities over time and on other websites or apps. Cookies are small pieces of information that
are stored by your browser on your computer’s hard drive to collect information about your
activities on our Website.
Cookies do not contain any Personal Information. We use cookies to collect and store
information for statistical purposes, including browsing and Service usage activity, and to
improve the services we provide. For example, if you are a registered user, we will use a cookie
to save your Service settings and to provide customizable and personalized services. Cookies
also enable you to select products, place them in your shopping cart and purchase the items. If
you select and purchase products on the Service, we keep a record of your browsing activity and
purchases. Most browsers allow you to refuse cookies from websites or to remove cookies from
your hard drive. If you choose to do this, you may not be able to access or use portions of the
Website.
INFORMATION USE
      We use Personal Information to:
             facilitate and improve the Service and our services;
             communicate with you; and
             promote Independent Business Owners.
      We may use aggregate information for any purpose, including for marketing purposes.
Internal and Service-Related Usage. Stella & Dot will use information, including Personal
Information, for internal, administrative, and service-related purposes. We may use and retain
any data we collect to provide and improve our services. For example, we use Personal
Information submitted by customers to process and complete the customer’s order, including for
shipping and billing purposes. We also use Personal Information submitted by Independent
Business Owners to calculate and process commissions.
                                                  3

Communications. We use a customer’s name, mailing address, email address and telephone
number for the following limited purposes:
        Sending emails for informational and operational purposes, such as account management
         or system maintenance;
        Monitoring and ensuring customer satisfaction, including troubleshooting problems and
         resolving disputes;
        Keeping you informed of new products and promotions at Stella & Dot Family Brands;
         and
        Sending you Stella & Dot Family Brands newsletters.
Promoting Independent Business Owners. Stella & Dot may, from time to time, publish an
Independent Business Owner’s Personal Information (for example, name, photograph, sales
results and achievements) to recognize the Independent Business Owner’s achievements and
help motivate other Independent Business Owners. These promotions will not contain Personal
Information about customers.
Aggregate Data. We may anonymize and aggregate data collected through the Service and use
it for any purpose. For example, we may aggregate usage and transaction information to provide
product recommendations to Website users.
INFORMATION DISCLOSURES
       We may share your information:
             with our third-party vendors and service providers;
             to refer you to an Independent Business Owner;
             to connect Independent Business Owners with other Independent Business
              Owners;
             to comply with legal obligations;
             to protect and defend our rights and property; and
             with your permission.
       We do not rent, sell, or share Personal Information about you with other people or
       nonaffiliated companies for their direct marketing purposes, unless we have your
       permission. We may share anonymous information for marketing and advertising
       purposes.
Vendors and Service Providers. We want to provide you with excellent service and make your
Stella & Dot Family Brands experience as seamless as possible. We share information, including
                                                   4

nonpublic Personal Information, with third parties that perform services on our behalf so we can
provide and improve our services. For example, we may disclose Personal Information for fraud
detection and prevention. These third parties must abide by this Privacy Policy and keep
nonpublic information confidential and use it only for its intended purpose.
Connect Independent Business Owners. To facilitate communications among our network of
Independent Business Owners, we may share Independent Business Owners’ contact information
with other Independent Business Owners.
Referrals. As part of our service and to make sure customer needs are met, we may refer
customers to an Independent Business Owner, such as when customers are not associated with an
Independent Business Owner in our systems or when customers request to host a Trunk Show.
We may share customer contact information with Independent Business Owners for these
purposes.
Marketing. We do not rent, sell, or share Personal Information about you with other people or
nonaffiliated companies for their direct marketing purposes, unless we have your permission.
We may allow access to other data collected by the Service to enable the delivery of online
advertising on the Service, or otherwise facilitate transmittal of information we think may be
useful or relevant to you.
We may show you personalized advertisements on other websites after you visit our Website and
our social media pages and websites.
You may be able to opt out of receiving personalized advertisements from advertisers or
advertising networks who are members of the Network Advertising Initiative or who subscribe to
the Digital Advertising Alliance’s Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising
by visiting the opt-out sections on the websites of each of those organizations. Links to those
sites are here:
Network Advertising Initiative: http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/
Digital Advertising Alliance: http://www.aboutads.info/choices/
When you opt out of personalized advertising, you may continue to see online advertising from
Stella & Dot Family Brands on other websites.
As Required By Law and Similar Disclosures. We may access, preserve, and disclose
collected information, if we believe doing so is required or appropriate to: comply with law
enforcement requests and legal process, such as a court order or subpoena; respond to your
requests; or protect your, our, or others’ rights, property, or safety.
Corporate Changes. We reserve the right to transfer Personal Information in the event Stella &
Dot acquires or merges with or is acquired by another company or during other corporate
changes. Any information disclosed as a result of one of these events or other corporate changes
will be subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time.
                                                    5

Your Permission. We may also disclose your Personal Information with your permission.
CHILDREN’S PRIVACY
We respect children’s privacy. We do not knowingly or intentionally collect or maintain Personal
Information from children under age 13, and no part of the Service is directed to children under
the age of 13. IF YOU ARE UNDER THE AGE OF 13, PLEASE DO NOT SUBMIT ANY
PERSONAL INFORMATION TO US. You should rely on a parent or guardian to assist you. If
you learn that your child has provided us with Personal Information without your consent, you
may alert us at privacy@stelladot.com. If we learn that we have collected any Personal
Information from children under 13, we will promptly take steps to delete such information and
terminate the child’s account.
INTERNATIONAL
You acknowledge that Stella & Dot is principally located in the United States and, accordingly,
your information may be transferred to, processed, and stored in the United States and that the
U.S. government, courts or law enforcement agencies may be able to obtain disclosure of your
information through lawful means in the U.S.
INFORMATION SECURITY
We take steps to ensure that your information is treated securely and in accordance with this
Privacy Policy. Unfortunately, the Internet cannot be guaranteed to be 100% secure, and we
cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you provide to us. We do not accept
liability for unintentional disclosure.
Please note that email is not encrypted and is not considered a secure means of transmitting
credit card numbers or other sensitive information. Stella & Dot will NEVER ask for sensitive
information via email.
By using the Service or providing Personal Information to us, you agree that we may
communicate with you electronically regarding security, privacy, and administrative issues
relating to your use of the Service. If we learn of a security system’s breach, we may attempt to
notify you electronically by posting a notice on the Service or sending an email to you. You may
have a legal right to receive this notice in writing. To receive free written notice of a security
breach (or to withdraw your consent from receiving electronic notice), please notify us at
privacy@stelladot.com.
YOUR CHOICES
You may review, correct, or delete your Personal Information through the Service. If you have
registered with us, you will be able to view and modify information contained in your personal
profile. However, for security purposes, you must contact Stella & Dot directly to change your
tax identification number or social security number. You may also contact us to remove any
Personal Information from our database.
                                                   6

U.S.-EU SAFE HARBOR
Stella & Dot adheres to the seven privacy principles dictated by the Safe Harbor Framework as
set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce: Notice, Choice, Onward Transfer, Security, Data
Integrity, Access and Enforcement. These principles may be found at:
www.export.gov/safeharbor.
Privacy Inquiries by EU Citizens
In compliance with the Safe Harbor Principles, Stella & Dot commits to resolve complaints
about your privacy and our collection or use of your Personal Information. EU citizens with
inquiries or complaints regarding this privacy policy should contact Stella & Dot LLC at
privacy@stelladot.com or by mail, Attn: Privacy Administrator, 1111 Bayhill Drive, Suite 375,
San Bruno, CA 94066.
Stella & Dot has further committed to refer unresolved complaints under the Safe Harbor
Principles to an independent dispute resolution mechanism, the BBB EU Safe Harbor, operated
by the Council of Better Business Bureaus. We ask that you contact us directly first. If you do
not receive timely acknowledgement of your inquiry or complaint, or if your inquiry or
complaint is not satisfactorily addressed by Stella & Dot, you may contact:
Council of Better Business Bureaus, Inc.
http://www.bbb.org/us/safe-harbor-complaints
COMPLIANCE WITH CANADA’S ANTI-SPAM LEGISLATION (“CASL”)
You may be asked to provide your Personal Information to opt-in to receive emails about Stella
& Dot’s Family Brands’ products, promotions, special offers and company updates. This
consent is sought by Stella & Dot LLC, 1111 Bayhill Drive, Suite 375, San Bruno, CA 94066.
You can unsubscribe at any time from these commercial electronic messages by using the
“unsubscribe link” located in the email, or by contacting us at privacy@stelladot.com or by mail,
Attn: Privacy Administrator, 1111 Bayhill Drive, Suite 375, San Bruno, CA 94066.
CHANGES TO PRIVACY POLICY AND QUESTIONS
This Policy may be amended, from time to time. If Stella & Dot decides to change its Privacy
Policy, we will post those changes and revise the “Last Updated” date at the bottom on the
Privacy Policy.
If you have questions about this Policy, please contact us at privacy@stelladot.com or by mail,
Attn: Privacy Administrator, 1111 Bayhill Drive, Suite 375, San Bruno, CA 94066.
Effective June 2014
Last Updated August 22, 2014
                                                  7
